Franz Boas Papers 1862-1942 Mss.B.B61.inventory3 Mss.B.B61.inventory03
American Philosophical Society
Franz Boas Papers: Inventory (C)
1862-1942
Mss.B.B61.inventory03
American Philosophical Society
1.0 section
This is part of the large inventory for the Franz Boas Papers (Mss B B61). For complete information concerning this collection, please view the Collection Description.
Boas, Franz, 1858-1942
Scope and Contents note
Due to the size of the collection, the content for Series I has been divided into multiple inventories. Please follow the links below to browse the inventories.
Inventories
Correspondents A
Correspondents B
Correspondents C
Correspondents D
Correspondents E-G
Correspondents H
Correspondents I-K
Correspondents L
Correspondents M
Correspondents N-Q
Correspondents R
Correspondents S
Correspondents T-V
Correspondents W-Z
- Franz Boas Papers - Correspondents C
  - C.R.B. Educational Foundation (Box 14)
    - From Boas re: Van veen, 1937 Apr. 5; 2p
    - To Boas, 1925 Dec. 31
      - from Olbrechts, F.M.
      - enc. with Olbrechts, F.M., 1926 Jan. 13
  - Cabanellas (Box 14)
    - From Pegram, G.B., 1937 Feb. 11
  - Cabella, C.F. (Box 14)
    - From Boas, 1925 Mar. 18; 1p
    - From Boas, 1925 Apr. 16; 1p
    - From Boas, 1925 May 27; 1p
    - From Boas, 1925 May 29; 1p
    - From Boas, 1929 Oct. 30; 1p
    - To Boas, 1924 Oct. 3; 3p
    - To Boas, 1925 May 27; 1p
    - To Boas, 1925 May 30; 1p
    - To Boas, 1929 Oct. 22; 4p
  - Cabrera, A.L. de (Box 14)
    - To Boas, 1923 Apr. 2; 2p
  - Cadena, L. (Box 14)
    - To Boas, 1912 Mar. 28
  - Cadien, J.C. (Box 14)
    - From Lehsten, E.E., 1917 June 14
  - Cadman, S.P. (Box 14)
    - From Boas, 1933, May 29
  - Cadwallader, Mrs. H.T. (Box 14)
    - From Boas, 1932 Apr. 7; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Feb. 16; 1p
  - Cadwallader, Mrs. Jane (Box 14)
    - From Boas, 1932 Oct. 20; 1p
    - From Boas, 1933 Sep. 14; 1p
    - To Boas, 1932 Nov. 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 Sep. 6; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 Sep. 30; 1p
  - Cadwallader, Mr. & Mrs. W.J. (Box 14)
    - From Boas, 1932 Apr. 7; 1p
    - From Boas, 1935 Nov. 25; 1p
    - To Boas (for Geo. Hunt), 1932 Mar. 26; 3p
    - To Boas (for Geo. Hunt), 1932 Apr. 23; 1p
    - To Boas (for Geo. Hunt), 1936 Mar. 4; 7p
    - To Boas (for Geo. Hunt), 1935 Nov. 9; 4p
  - Cady, G. (Box 14)
    - From Boas, 1934 Oct. 29; 1p
  - Cadzow, Donald A. (Box 14)
    - To Boas, 1938 Mar. 29; 1p
  - Caillé, Augustus (Box 14)
    - From Boas, 1905 Jan. 2; 1p
  - Cain, Julien (Box 14)
    - From Boas, 1932 Dec. 16; 1p
    - To Boas, 1932 Dec. 6; 1p
  - Calder, W.M. (Box 14)
    - From Parsons, E.C., 1917 Nov. 3
    - To Parsons, E.C., 1917 Dec. 19
  - Caldwell, R.J. (Box 14)
    - From Boas, 1933 Nov. 24; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 Nov. 6; 1p
  - Caldwell, William A. (Box 14)
    - To Boas, 1941 May 13; 1p
  - Caldwin, (?) R. (Box 14)
    - To Boas, 1917 Aug. 10
  - Calilsla, E. (Box 14)
    - To Boas, 1931 Dec. 2; 2p
  - Caliver, A. (Box 14)
    - From Boas, 1933 July 24; 1p
  - Calkins, Gary N. (Box 14)
    - From Boas, 1941 Nov. 13; 1p
  - Call to All Active Supporters of Democracy and Peace (Box 14)
    - From Boas, 1939 July 20; 2p
  - Call to American Congress for Peace and Democracy, 1933 Sept (Box 14)
  - Caluza, Reuben T. (Box 14)
    - From Boas, 1936 June 2; 1p
    - See Boas open letter, 1936 Jan. 22
    - To Boas, 1936 Apr. 23; 2p
    - To Boas, 1936 Sep. 14; 2p
  - Calverton, V.F. (Box 14)
    - From Boas, 1929 Mar. 20; 1p
    - To Boas, 1928 Feb. 21; 3p
    - To Boas, 1931 May 13; 1p
      General note
      (Ramconcelli - Calzia)
  - Calzia, G.P. (Box 14)
    - From Boas, 1927 May 31; 1p
    - From Boas, 1929 Dec. 13; 1p
    - From Boas, 1930 June 6; 1p
    - To Boas, 1925 Oct. 19; 4p
    - To Boas, 1927 Feb. 14; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 May 16; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 June 30; 1p
    - To Boas, 1929 Nov. 30; 1p
  - Camara Cascudo, L. da (Box 14)
    - From Boas, 1935 July 16; 1p
    - To Boas, 1935 Feb. 14; 1p
    - To Boas, 1935 June 7; 1p
  - Camboa, R. (Box 14)
    - To Boas, 1912 Mar. 23
  - Cambridge Univ. Registrar (Box 14)
    - From Boas, 1937 Feb. 8; 1p
  - Camehl, R.W. -- from Boas, 1911 Apr. 10 (Box 14)
  - Cameron, S.P. (Box 14)
    - From Boas, 1918 Apr. 30; 1p
  - Camp, W.M. (Box 14)
    - From Boas, 1917 Apr. 26
    - To Boas, 1917 Apr. 16
  - Campbell, Harold G. (Box 14)
    - From Boas, 1934 Nov. 26; 1p
    - From Boas, 1942 May 25; 1p
    - To Boas, 1934 Nov. 27; 1p
  - Campbell, W.S. (Box 14)
    - From Boas, 1916 Oct. 6
    - To Boas, 1916 Oct. 1
  - Campos, N. (Box 14)
    - To Boas (receipt), 1912 May 6
  - Camsell, C. (Box 14)
    - From Boas, 1924 May 24; 2p
    - To Boas, 1924 May 26; 1p
  - Camuna, M. (Box 14)
    - To N.Y. Acad. of Sci., 1917 Aug. 21
  - Canada, Dept. of Indian Affairs (Box 14)
    - 1890 May 8
    - To Boas, 1891 July 4
  - Canada, Legation Secretary (Box 14)
    - From Boas, 1931 May 4; 1p
  - Canadian Bank of Commerce, Vancouver (Box 14)
    - From Boas, 1930 Nov. 20; 1p
    - To Boas (statement), 1930 Oct. 27
  - Canadian Pacific Navigation Co. (Box 14)
    - From Boas, 1899 May 18; 1p
    - From Boas, 1899 July 31; 1p
    - From Boas, 1900 Jan. 27; 1p
    - From Boas, 1900 Oct. 23; 1p
    - From Boas, 1907 Apr. 1
  - Canal, C.S. (Box 14)
    - To Boas, 1931 May 13; 1p
  - Canby, Henry S. (Box 14)
    - To Boas, 1941 July 17; 2p
  - Cane, G. (Box 14)
    - From Boas, 1935 Mar. 18; 2p
  - Canfield, J.H. (Librarian, Columbia U.) (Box 14)
    - From Boas, 1903 May 27; 1p
    - From Boas, 1903 Aug. 20; 3p
    - From Boas, 1903 Aug. 28; 1p
    - From Boas, 1903 Sep. 25; 1p
    - From Boas, 1903 Oct. 16; 2p
      - (4 pp. book list inc.), 1903 Nov. 27; 5p
    - From Boas, 1904 Mar. 10; 2p
    - From Boas, 1905 Oct. 24
    - From Boas, 1905 Dec. 16
    - From Boas, 1905 Dec. 26
    - To Boas, 1903 May 18
    - To Boas, 1903 May 28
    - To Boas, 1903 June 12
    - To Boas, 1903 June 12; 1p
    - To Boas, 1903 Oct. 17; 1p
    - To Boas, 1904 Mar. 9; 2p
    - To Boas, 1905 Mar. 28
    - To Boas, 1905 Oct. 23
    - To Boas, 1905 Oct. 25
    - To Boas, 1905 Nov. 6
    - To Boas, 1905 Dec. 18
  - Cann (?), Paul (Box 14)
    - To Boas, 1917 July 5
  - Cannon, C.L. (Box 14)
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 21; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Oct. 19; 1p
  - Cannon, Walter B. (Box 14)
    - From Boas (see FB to Wheeler, W.M., same date), 1933 May 23
    - (see FB to Carlson, A.J., same date), 1941 July 31
    - To Boas, 1933 May 26; 1p
    - To Boas, 1938 Jan. 29; 1p
    - (see FB open letter on culture and democracy in Spain. Replies.), 1938 Jan.
    - (see McConnell, F.J.), 1938 Apr. 20
    - To Boas, 1940 Dec. 4
    - To Boas, 1941 Nov. 7; 1p
  - Canseco, M. (Box 14)
    - To Boas, 1912 Jan. 5
    - To Boas, 1912 Mar. 11
    - To Boas, 1912 Mar. 16
    - To Boas, 1912 May 7
  - Cantarella, Michele F. (Box 14)
    - To McAvoy, C.T., 1938 Jan. 28
  - Cantor, N. (Box 14)
    - From Boas, 1925 Apr. 17; 1p
    - To Boas, 1925 Apr. 20; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 Mar. 28; 1p
  - Cape (?) (Box 14)
    - To Boas, 1906 Mar. 17
  - Capen, S.P. (Box 14)
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 11; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Oct. 12; 1p
    - To Duggan, S.P., 1920 Oct. 9; 1p
  - Capistrano de Abreu, J. (Box 14)
    - From Boas, 1923 Jan. 15; 1p
    - From Boas, 1923 Jan. 16; 1p
    - From Boas, 1923 Mar. 10; 1p
    - From Boas, 1923 Mar. 23; 1p
    - To Boas, 1923 Jan. 20; 1p
  - Capitan, J. (Box 14)
    - From Boas, 1909 June 1; 3p
    - From Boas, 1910 Jan. 13
    - From Boas, 1910 Jan. 28
    - see FB to Gordon, G.B., 1910 Nov. 11
    - see FB to Butler, N.M., 1910 Nov. 26
    - see FB to Butler N.M., 1910 Dec. 19
    - see FB to Butler N.M., 1911 Jan. 4
    - From Boas, 1911 Jan. 6
    - From Boas, 1911 Jan. 25
    - From Boas, 1911 Jan. 27
    - From Boas, 1911 Mar. 27
    - From Boas, 1913 June 16
    - To Boas, 1910 Apr. 26
    - To Boas, 1911 Jan. 28; 4p
    - To Boas, 1911 Dec. 21; 5p
    - To Boas, 1914 May 8
  - Capps, E. (Box 14)
    - From Boas, 1933 June 5; 1p
  - Carana, V.V. (Box 14)
    - To Boas, 1917 Aug. 12
  - Cardenas, J.F. de (Box 14)
    - From Boas, 1940 Dec. 5; 1p
  - Cardozo, B.N. (Box 14)
    - To Seligman, E.R., 1926 Mar. 8; 1p
    - (enc. with Seligman, E.R., 1926 Mar. 31)
  - Careaga, Luis (Box 14)
    - From Boas, 1937 Sept. 13; 1p
    - To Boas, 1937 Sept. 13; 1p
  - Carey, Robt. (Box 14)
    - From Boas, (1900?)1908 Oct. 22; 2p
  - Carfomtu (?) (Box 14)
    - To Boas, 1903 Aug. 2
    - To Boas, 1904 Mar. 7
  - Carl Schurz Memorial Foundation (Box 14)
    - From Boas, 1930 July 29; 1p
      Scope and Contents note
      See Corwine, Wm. R.
      See Gramm, Hanns
  - Carleton, G.A. (Box 14)
    - To Boas, 1900 Feb. 9 and Oct. 30
  - Carlson, A.J. (Box 14)
    - From Boas, 1940 May 24; 1p
    - From Boas, 1941 July 31; 1p
    - To Boas, 1940 Dec. 19; 1p
    - To Gideonse. H.D., 1941 Oct. 11; 1p
  - Carlson, C.L. (Box 14)
    - From Boas, 1931 Mar. 18; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Mar. 14; 1p
  - Carlson, Valdemar (Box 14)
    - From Boas, 1939 Dec. 14; 1p
    - To Boas, 1939 Dec. 12; 1p
  - Carlton, W.N.C. (Box 14)
    - From Boas, 1912 Oct. 10
    - To Boas, Oct. 7 & 14 1912
  - Carman, H.J. (Box 14)
    - From Boas, 1939 Mar. 30; 1p
    - see FB to Lombardo, C.J., 1940 Oct. 14
    - see Pegram, G.B. to Cabanellas, 1937 Feb. 11
  - Carmichael, R.D. (Box 14)
    - 1938 Jan.
      see FB open letter, Spain
  - Carmon, W. (Box 14)
    - From Boas, 1930 Apr. 28; 1p
    - To Boas, 1930 Dec. 31?; 1p
  - Carnegie, Andrew (Box 14)
    - From Boas, 1906 Nov. 30
    - From Boas, 1906 Dec. 6
    - From Boas, 1908 Dec. 1; 2p
    - From Boas, 1914 Nov. 23; 2p
  - Carnegie Corporation of New York (Box 14)
    see Keppel, Frederick P.
  - Carnegie Endowment for International Peace (Box 14)
    See Scott, James Brown
    See Haskell, Henry S.
  - Carnegie Foundation (Box 14)
    - Suzzalo, Henry, 1932 June 2
  - Carnegie Institution (Box 14)
    - From Boas, 1920 Aug. 16; 1p
      See Merriam, John C. Gilbert, W.M. Woodward, R.S.
  - Carnegie Inst., New York (Box 14)
    - From Boas? (report), 1902 June 28; 5p
    - From Boas, 1903 Jan. 9; 4p
    - From Boas, 1903 Nov. 14; 1p
    - From Boas, 1904 Jan. 18; 2p
    - From Boas, 1904 Dec. 13; 8p
  - Carney, Mabel (Box 14)
    - From Boas, 1936 Feb. 3; 1p
    - From Boas, 1940 Jan. 8; 1p
    - From Boas, 1935 Apr. 3; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Jan. 22; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Oct. 8; 2p
    - To Boas, 1939 Dec. 29; 1p
    - MC -- from Kalibala, E.B., 1939 Dec. 28
    - MC -- from Jones, T.J., 1936 Feb. 6
  - Carolyn -- (see Adler, Carolyn)
  - Carpenter, Ann M. (Box 14)
    - To Kinnicutt, Frances, 1906; 4p
  - Carpenter, Fanny H. (Box 14)
    - To Boas, 1906 Jan. 26; 1p
  - Carpenter, G.R. (Box 14)
    - From Boas, 1903; 1p
    - To Boas, 1903 Oct. 26; 1p
    - Field study, 1906 Oct. 16; 3p
  - Carpenter, J. Estlin (Box 14)
    - From Boas, 1908 June 22; 1p
    - To Boas, 1908 June 30; 2p
    - To Boas, 1908 Aug. 29; 1p
  - Carpenter, Prof. Niles (Box 14)
    - From Boas, 1936 Mar. 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Mar. 6; 1p
  - Carpenter, William H. (Box 14)
    - From Boas, 1904 Dec. 13; 1p
    - From Boas, 1904 Dec. 14; 1p
    - From Boas, 1905 May 8; 1p
    - From Boas, 1905 Mar. 11; 1p
    - From Boas, 1905 Oct. 5
    - From Boas, 1905 Nov. 1; 1p
    - See FB to Adams, E.D., 1905 Nov. 1
    - From Boas, 1905 Nov. 21; 1p
    - From Boas, 1905 Dec. 12; 1p
    - From Boas, 1906 Oct. 4; 1p
    - From Boas, 1906 Nov. 15; 1p
    - From Boas, 1907 Mar. 1
    - From Boas, 1908 Nov. 10
    - See letter to Butler, N.M., 1908 Nov. 10
    - From Boas, 1909 May 12
    - From Boas, 1913 Oct. 4
    - From Boas, 1914 Feb. 12
    - From Boas, 1914 Feb. 13
    - From Boas, 1919 Oct. 8; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Jan. 5; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 May 14; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 May 20; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 July 20; 1p
    - enc. purchase list, German & Austrian libraries, 1920 July 29; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Sept. 29; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Dec. 15; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Dec. 30; 1p
    - From Boas, 1921 Dec. 16; 1p
    - From Boas, 1922 Jan. 4; 1p
    - To Boas, 1899 Mar. 9; 1p
    - To Boas, 1903 Aug. 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1904 Mar. 7; 2p
    - To Boas, 1904 Nov. 30; 3p
    - To Boas, 1904 Dec. 14
    - To Boas, 1904 Dec. 16; 1p
    - To Boas, 1905 Feb. 27; 3p
    - To Boas, 1905 Mar. 13; 1p
    - To Boas, 1905 May 20; 1p
    - To Boas, 1905 Nov. 6; 1p
    - To Boas, 1905 Dec. 31; 2p
    - To Boas, 1906 Jan. 3; 1p
    - To Boas, 1906 Jan. 6; 1p
    - To Boas, 1906 Jan. 14; 2p
    - To Boas, 1906 May 16
    - To Boas, 1906 Oct. 4
    - To Boas, 1906 Dec. 5
    - To Boas, 1909 May 13
    - To Boas, 1913 Jan. 23
    - To Boas, 1913 Mar. 5 - 1914 Feb. 12; 2p
    - To Boas, 1914 Feb. 13
    - To Boas, 1917 May 15
    - To Boas, 1919 Oct. 10
    - To Boas, 1920 May 17; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 July 16; 2p
    - To Boas, 1920 July 26; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Aug. 14; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Oct. 1; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Oct. 4; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Dec. 23; 1p
    - To Boas, 1923 Jan. 6; 1p
    - To WHC from Parsons, E.C., 1917 Mar. 27
  - Carpenter, Mrs. W.H. (Anna M.) (Box 14)
    - From Boas, 1906 Feb. 3; 1p
    - From Boas, 1906 Feb. 6; 1p
    - To Boas, 1906 Feb. 4; 5p
  - Carpentier, -- to Boas, 1905 July 24 (Box 14)
  - Carr, C.E. (Box 14)
    - From Boas, 1905 July 24
  - Carreno, Alberto Maria (Box 14)
    - From Boas, 1920 Apr. 27; 1p
    - To Boas, 1912 Mar. 23
    - To Boas, 1920 Apr. 17; 1p
  - Carrick, C.L. (Box 14)
    - To Hart, A.C., 1910 Aug. 11; 2p
  - Carrington, Fitz Roy (Box 14)
    - To Keppel, Fred, 1908 Oct. 26
  - Carroll, Michelle (Box 14)
    - From Boas, 1914 Sep. 29
    - To Boas, 1909 Oct. 15
    - To Boas, 1909 Dec. 17
    - To Boas, 1914 Oct. 2
  - Carta, J. (Box 14)
    - To Gini, Corrado, 1920 July 6; 2p
    - To Gini, Corrado, 1920 July 12; 1p
  - Carter, A.E. (Box 14)
    - From Boas, 1910 May 5; 2p
    - To Boas, 1910 May 7
  - Carter, A.P. (Box 14)
    - To Boas, 1917 May 9; 2p
  - Carter, A&W (Box 14)
    - From Boas, 1936 Jan. 2; 1p
  - Carter, Ara (Box 14)
    - From Boas, 1933 Jan. 16; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 Jan. 12; 1p
  - Carter, Arletta Warriner (Box 14)
    - To Gordon, Paul W., 1933 Sep. 30; 1p
      - enc. to BF from Gordon, Paul, dated Oct. 2, 1933
    - To Boas, 1935 Dec. 27; 1p
    - To Boas, 1935 Dec. 28; 1p
  - Carter, E.A. (Box 14)
    - From Boas, 1930 Nov. 11; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 Jan. 31; 1p
    - To Boas, 1930 Nov. 6; 1p
  - Carter, E.C. (Box 14)
    - To Boas, 1927 May 27; 1p
  - Carter, Isabel G. (Mrs. Hugh) (Box 14)
    - From Boas, 1925 July 30; 2p
    - From Boas, 1925 Dec. 1; 1p
    - From Boas, 1926 Mar. 2; 1p
    - From Boas, 1926 Mar. 4; 1p
    - From Boas, 1926 Mar. 12; 1p
    - From Boas, 1926 May 12; 1p
    - From Boas, 1926 Oct. 18; 1p
    - From Boas, 1926 Oct. 26; 1p
    - From Boas, 1926 Oct. 27; 2p
    - From Boas, 1926 Nov. 6; 1p
    - From Boas, 1928 Nov. 7; 1p
    - From Boas, 1940 Dec. 5; 1p
    - From Boas, 1941 Jan. 20; 1p
    - From Boas, 1941 Feb. 17; 1p
    - To Boas, 1925 Dec. 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1926 Feb. 8; 1p
    - To Boas, 1926 Feb. 18; 2p
    - To Boas, 1926 Feb. 28; 1p
    - To Boas, 1926 Mar. 10; 1p
    - To Boas, 1926 Mar. 16; 1p
    - To Boas, 1926 Mar.?; 1p
    - To Boas, 1926 Apr. 28; 3p
    - To Boas, 1926 June?; 7p
    - To Boas, 1926 July 13; 1p
    - To Boas, 1926 Sep. 29; 1p
    - To Boas, 1926 Oct. 23; 2p
    - To Boas, 1926 Nov. 4; 2p
    - To Boas, 1928 Nov. 14; 1p
    - To Boas, 1940 Dec. 13; 1p
    - To Boas, 1941 Jan. 21; 1p
    - To Boas, 1941 Feb. 15; 1p
  - Carter, W.S. (Box 14)
    - To Boas, 1934 Mar. 13; 1p
  - Carus, Paul (Box 14)
    - From Boas, 1903 Nov. 4; 1p
    - To Boas, 1903 Oct. 31; 2p
    - To Holmes, W.H., 1906 May 17
  - Carver, George Washington (Box 14)
    - From Boas, 1940 June 3; 1p
    - To Boas, 1940 June 12; 1p
  - Carver, T.M. (Box 14)
    - From Boas, 1920 Aug. 5; 1p
  - Cary, Clarence (Box 14)
    - From Boas, 1904 Jan. 18; 1p
    - To Boas, 1904 Feb. 17; 1p
    - To Boas, 1905 Mar. 6
    - To Boas, 1905 Dec. 21
  - Casalduero, Joaquin (Box 14)
    - see FB open letter, Spain, 1938 Jan.
  - Casanova, P. Gonzalez (Box 14)
    - From Boas, 1929 Jan. 2; 1p
    - From Boas, 1929 Jan. 29; 1p
    - From Boas, 1930 Mar. 5; 1p
    - From Boas, 1930 Apr. 2; 1p
    - From Boas, 1930 June 4; 1p
    - From Boas, 1933 Sep. 18; 1p
    - To Boas, 1928 Dec. 25; 2p
    - To Boas, 1929 Jan. 17; 2p
    - To Boas, 1930 May 24; 2p
    - To Boas, 1932 Dec. 20; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1933 Oct. 16; 1p
  - Caso, Alfonso (Box 14)
    - From Boas, 1933 June 5; 1p
    - From Boas, 1933 June 7; 1p
    - From Boas, 1939 June 14; 1p
    - To Boas, 1930 Apr. 11; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 May 29; 1p
    - To Boas, 1939 June 6; 1p
    - To Boas, 1939 June 22; 1p
  - Cassidy, Mary M. (Box 14)
    - From Boas, 1936 May 13; 1p
  - Cassirer, Ernst (Box 14)
    - From Boas, 1937 June 14; 1p
  - Castaneda, D. (Box 14)
    - To Boas, 1935 Aug. 12; 1p
  - Castaneda, G.R. (Box 14)
    - To Boas, 1915 Feb. 21
  - Castaneda, Isabel R. (Box 14)
    - To Boas, 1911 Aug. 10; 2p
  - Castedello, W. (Box 14)
    - To Boas, 1914 July 16
  - Castellanos, Abraham (Box 14)
    Native American Images note
    Mayan picture-writing.
    - From Boas, 1917 Aug. 1
    - To Boas, 1916 Aug. 9
    - To Boas, 1916 Sep. 11 & Oct. 22
    - To Boas, 1917 Apr. 30; 3p
    - To Boas, 1917 June 30; 11p
    - To Boas, 1917 July 1
    - To Boas, 1917 July 31; 10p
  - Castellanos, C.A. (Box 14)
    - From Boas, 1919 Oct. 14; 1p
  - Castellanos, I. (Box 14)
    - To Boas, 1922 Dec. 17; 2p
  - Castillo LedC3n, L. (Box 14)
    - From Boas, 1921 Sep. 9; 1p
    - From Boas, 1921 Nov. 18; 2p
    - From Boas, 1922 Nov. 1; 2p
    - From Boas, 1922 Nov. 6; 2p
    - To Boas, 1921 May 20; 1p
    - To Boas, 1922 Oct.; 1p
    - To Boas, 1922 Nov. 29
    - To Boas, 1923 Jan. 13; 1p
    - LCD -- to Toussaint, C.M. and newspaper clippings, 1922 July 24; 2p
  - Caswell, Mary (Box 14)
    - To Müller, Margarethe, 1906 Feb. 2; 1p
    - To Müller, Margarethe, 1906 Feb. 19; 1p
  - Cateollanos, I. (Box 14)
    - To Boas, 1927 June 8; 1p
  - Catholic Church in Spain (Box 14)
    - see enc. Rios, F. de los, 1937 Sep. 14
    - see enc. FB to Searles, R.W., 1937 Sep. 17
    - Statement re Church, 1937 Oct.?
  - Catlin, F.W. (Box 14)
    - From Boas, 1908 Oct. 10
  - Catt, Carrie Chapman (Box 15)
    - To Boas with 4 cosigners such as Einstein, Albert, 1937 Feb. 10; 1p
  - Cattell, J. McKeen (Box 15)
    - From Boas, 1903 Oct. 26; 1p
    - From Boas, 1905 May 24
    - From Boas, 1907 Mar. 29
    - From Boas, 1910 Mar. 16
    - From Boas, 1910 July 2
    - From Boas, 1913 Oct. 7; 2p
    - From Boas, 1913 Oct. 8
    - From Boas, 1913 Dec. 1
    - From Boas, 1914 Dec. 1
    - From Boas, 1916 Oct. 25
    - From Boas, 1917 Jan. 11
    - From Boas, 1917 Jan. 15
    - From Boas, 1917 Jan. 29
    - From Boas, 1917 Feb. 20
    - From Boas, 1917 Mar. 13
    - From Boas, 1917 May 19
    - From Boas, 1917 Oct. 2; 2p
    - From Boas, 1918 Feb. 20; 1p
    - From Boas, 1918 Mar. 9; 1p
    - From Boas, 1918 Apr. 12; 2p
    - From Boas, 1918 Oct. 3; 1p
    - From Boas, 1919 May 20; 1p
    - From Boas, 1919 Aug. 13; 2p
    - From Boas, 1919 Sep. 4; 1p
    - From Boas, 1919 Oct. 8; 1p
    - From Boas, 1919 Oct. 31; 1p
    - From Boas, 1919 Dec. 2; 2p
    - From Boas, 1919 Dec. 5; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 May 5; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 July 19; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Aug. 2; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Aug. 9; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 7; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 11; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 18; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 28; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Dec. 30; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Dec. 31; 1p
    - From Boas, 1921 Nov. 14; 1p
    - From Boas, 1923 Jan. 30
    - From Boas, 1923 Apr. 30; 1p
    - From Boas, 1926 Jan. 4; 1p
    - From Boas, 1926 July 9; 1p
    - From Boas, 1927 Nov. 30; 1p
    - From Boas, 1927 Dec. 3; 1p
    - From Boas, 1927 Dec. 8; 1p
    - From Boas, 1928 June 18; 1p
    - From Boas, 1928 Nov. 1; 1p
    - From Boas, 1928 Dec. 15; 1p
    - From Boas, 1929 Dec. 6; 1p
    - From Boas, 1930 May 23; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 Apr. 1; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 May 28; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 Dec. 23; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 Dec. 8; 1p
    - From Boas, 1933 Apr. 18; 1p
    - From Boas, 1933 June 5; 1p
    - From Boas, 1933 Sep. 25; 2p
    - From Boas, 1936 Sep. 14; 1p
    - From Boas, 1936 Nov. 20; 1p
    - From Boas, 1938 Dec. 8; 1p
    - From Boas, 1938 Dec. 19; 1p
    - From Boas, 1939 Jan. 13; 1p
    - From Boas, 1940 June 20; 1p
    - From Boas, 1940 Oct. 14; 1p
    - From Boas, 1941 June 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1894 Dec. 14
    - To Boas, 1895 Jan. 7
    - To Boas, 1895 Feb. 20; 2p
    - To Boas, 1895 Mar. 4
    - To Boas, 1895 Dec. 2
    - To Boas, 1896 Mar. 19
    - To Boas, 1896 May 4
    - To Boas, 1896 May 9
    - To Boas, 1896 June 20
    - To Boas, 1898 Dec. 3
    - To Boas, 1899 May 14
    - To Boas, 1899 Sep. 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1903 Aug. 11; 1p
    - To Boas, 1903 Aug. 22; 1p
    - enc. letter to Harrison, 1903 Aug. 29; 3p
    - To Boas, 1903 Sep. 5; 1p
    - To Boas, 1903 Sep. 14; 1p
    - To Boas, 1905 July 5
    - To Boas, 1905 Aug. 14
    - To Boas, 1905 Sep. 11
    - To Boas, 1905 Nov. 4
    - To Boas, 1905 Dec. 26
    - To Boas, 1906 Jan. 14
    - To Boas, 1906 Jan. 20
    - To Boas, 1906 Mar. 24
    - To Boas, 1906 May 19
    - To Boas, 1906 May 31
    - To Boas, 1906 Aug. 2, 1909 Mar. 6; 3p
    - To Boas, 1910 July 4
    - To Boas, 1912 Jan. 3; 2p
    - To Boas, 1912 Feb. 26
    - To Boas, 1912 Mar. 13; 2p
    - To Boas, 1912 Oct. 29
    - To Boas, 1913 May 13; 10p
    - To Boas, 1914 Nov. 27
    - To Boas, 1915 Nov. 8
    - To Boas, 1916 June 9
    - To Boas, 1916 June 22; 2p
    - To Boas, 1916 June 28
    - To Boas, 1916 Oct. 23
    - To Boas, 1917 Jan. 13
    - To Boas, 1917 Feb. 10
    - To Boas, 1917 Feb. 28
    - To Boas, 1917 Mar. 19
    - To Boas, 1917 May 26
    - To Boas, 1917 May 31; 2p
    - To Boas, 1917 June 9; 5p
    - To Boas, 1917 June 26; 2p
    - To Boas, 1917 Nov. 15; 2p
    - To Boas, 1918 Feb. 21; 1p
    - To Boas, 1918 Mar. 8; 1p
    - To Boas, 1918 Apr. 4; 1p
    - To Boas, 1918 Apr. 14; 1p
    - To Boas, 1918 Oct. 8; 1p
    - To Boas, 1918 Oct. 15; 1p
    - To Boas, 1918 Oct. 23; 1p
    - To Boas, 1918 Oct. 30; 2p
    - To Boas, 1919 May 19; 1p
    - To Boas, 1919 Sep. 18; 1p
    - To Boas, 1919 Sep. 25; 1p
    - To Boas, 1919 Oct. 1; 1p
    - To Boas, 1919 Oct. 11; 1p
    - To Boas, 1919 Oct. 23; 1p
    - To Boas, 1919 Dec. 4; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 May 12; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 July 16; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Aug. 6; 2p
    - To Boas, 1920 Oct. 23; 1p
    - To Boas, 1921 Feb. 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1923 Feb. 8; 1p
    - To Boas, 1926 Jan. 7; 1p
    - To Boas, 1926 May 8; 1p
    - To Boas, 1926 Sep. 29; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 Dec. 5; 1p
    - To Boas, 1928 Nov. 3; 1p
    - To Boas, 1929 Dec. 11; 1p
    - To Boas, 1930 May 29; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Mar. 18; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Mar. 30; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 May 27; 1p
    - see FB to Woodworth, R.S., 1931 Sep. 2
    - To Boas, 1932 Mar. 16; 1p
    - To Boas, 1932 Dec. 9; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 June 3; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 June 6; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 Sep. 30; 1p
    - To Boas, 1938 Dec. 10; 1p
    - To Boas, 1939 Mar. 4; 1p
    - To Boas, 1940 June 11; 1p
    - To Boas, 1940 Oct. 10; 1p
    - To Boas, 1942 Apr. 25; 1p
    - Chase, H.W. re G. Saslow, 1936 Sep. 22; 1p
    - Voorhis, H.O. -- to G. Saslow, 1936 Jan. 28
    - To Columbia U. Council, 1918 Dec. 6; 1p
    - To Columbia U. Trustees, 1918 Mar. 26; 3p
      - (enc., see JMC to FB), 1918 Apr. 4
    - To Columbia U. Trustees, 1921 Sep. 21; 5p
    - To Coulter, J.M., 1918 Mar. 30; 8p
      - (enc., see JMC to FB), 1918 Apr. 4
    - To Dampf, A., 1933 July 13k
    - To Ed., The Evening Post, 1917 June 26; 3p
    - To Gregory, T.W., 1918 June 27; 1p
    - (above to JMC), 1918 July 8
    - To Seligman, E.R.A., 1917 Mar. 8; 2p